<?xml version="1.0" encoding="Windows-1252" ?>
<XML_DIZ_INFO>
<MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
    <MASTER_PAD_VERSION>1.15</MASTER_PAD_VERSION>
    <MASTER_PAD_INFO>Portable Application Description, or PAD for short, is a data set that is used by shareware authors to disseminate information to anyone interested in their software products. To find out more go to http://www.asp-shareware.org/pad</MASTER_PAD_INFO>
</MASTER_PAD_VERSION_INFO>
<Company_Info>
        <Company_Name>Newton Software</Company_Name>
        <Address_1>18 Dilston Ave</Address_1>
        <City_Town>Whitley Bay</City_Town>
        <State_Province>Tyne & Wear</State_Province>
        <Zip_Postal_Code>NE25 8QG</Zip_Postal_Code>
        <Country>United Kingdom</Country>
        <Company_WebSite_URL>http://newtonsoftware.co.uk</Company_WebSite_URL>
<Contact_Info>
        <Author_First_Name>Tim</Author_First_Name>
        <Author_Last_Name>Newton</Author_Last_Name>
        <Author_Email>tim@newtonsoftware.co.uk</Author_Email>
        <Contact_First_Name>Tim</Contact_First_Name>
        <Contact_Last_Name>Newton</Contact_Last_Name>
        <Contact_Email>tim@newtonsoftware.co.uk</Contact_Email>
    </Contact_Info>
<Support_Info>
        <Sales_Email>tim@newtonsoftware.co.uk</Sales_Email>
        <Support_Email>tim@newtonsoftware.co.uk</Support_Email>
        <General_Email>tim@newtonsoftware.co.uk</General_Email>
        <Sales_Phone />
        <Support_Phone />
        <General_Phone />
        <Fax_Phone />
    </Support_Info>
</Company_Info>
<Program_Info>
        <Program_Name>Clone</Program_Name>
        <Program_Version>2.0.1</Program_Version>
        <Program_Release_Month>02</Program_Release_Month>
        <Program_Release_Day>24</Program_Release_Day>
        <Program_Release_Year>2003</Program_Release_Year>
        <Program_Cost_Dollars>30</Program_Cost_Dollars>
        <Program_Cost_Other_Code />
        <Program_Cost_Other />
        <Program_Type>Demo</Program_Type>
        <Program_Release_Status>Major Update</Program_Release_Status>
        <Program_Install_Support>Install Only</Program_Install_Support>
        <Program_OS_Support>Win95,Win98,WinME,WinNT 3.x,WinNT 4.x,WinXP,Windows2000</Program_OS_Support>
        <Program_Language>English</Program_Language>
<File_Info>
        <Filename_Versioned>clone.exe</Filename_Versioned>
        <Filename_Previous>clone.exe</Filename_Previous>
        <Filename_Generic>clone.exe</Filename_Generic>
        <Filename_Long>clone.exe</Filename_Long>
        <File_Size_Bytes>3938304</File_Size_Bytes>
        <File_Size_K>3846</File_Size_K>
        <File_Size_MB>3.75</File_Size_MB>
    </File_Info>
<Expire_Info>
        <Has_Expire_Info>Y</Has_Expire_Info>
        <Expire_Count>30</Expire_Count>
        <Expire_Based_On>Days</Expire_Based_On>
        <Expire_Other_Info />
        <Expire_Month />
        <Expire_Day />
        <Expire_Year />
    </Expire_Info>
        <Program_Change_Info />
        <Program_Specific_Category>Utilities</Program_Specific_Category>
        <Program_Categories>utilities,screen saverd</Program_Categories>
        <Program_System_Requirements />
        <Includes_JAVA_VM>N</Includes_JAVA_VM>
        <Includes_VB_Runtime>Y</Includes_VB_Runtime>
        <Includes_DirectX>N</Includes_DirectX>
</Program_Info>
<Program_Descriptions>
<English>
        <Keywords>Clone file backup utility screensaver screen saver Tim Newton synchronisation sync synchronization replicate software configuration management CDRW CD-RW UNC path newtonsoftware newton software clone</Keywords>
        <Char_Desc_45>A backup tool that can run as a screen saver</Char_Desc_45>
        <Char_Desc_80>A backup utility that also runs as a screen saver. Copies files to any path</Char_Desc_80>
        <Char_Desc_250>Clone is a backup utility that also runs as a screen saver. Clone copies files to any media that can be mapped to a windows drive or UNC path, e.g. CDRW</Char_Desc_250>
        <Char_Desc_450>Clone allows you to backup your files. Clone can be run as either a screen saver or as a standard windows utility. Run as a screensave, clone backups up the data that is important to you while you take a break from your computer. This ensures you have a copy of your most important files backed up. Clone copies files from one location to another. This can be another hard disk, your CR-RW drive or any other media mapped to a drive or UNC path.</Char_Desc_450>
        <Char_Desc_2000>Clone allows you to backup your files. Clone can be run as either a screen saver or as a standard windows utility. Run as a screensave, clone backups up the data that is important to you while you take a break from your computer. This ensures you have a copy of your most important files backed up. 
Clone copies files from one location to another. This can be another directory on your hard disk, another hard disk altogether, your CR-RW drive, your floppy disk / zip disk or a network file server. Clone will copy files to any media that can be mapped as a windows directory. As well as making a backup copy you can specify clone keeps old versions of your files, allowing you to go back to a previous version of a file if required. Clone is incredible easy to run and configure.
Clone keeps a track of how many files it has checked and copied so you always know what the program is doing. 
Main Features 
1) Backup files and directories to a defined location - as many as you like 
2) Uses the date and time, file size or the archive attribute to determine if a file should be copied 
3) Run as a standard windows utility or as a screen saver 
4) If using screen saver mode you can still run your favourite screen saver as well 
5) Backup to any media (including CD-RW) that can be mapped to a windows drive or UNC path 
6) Schedule backs to occur at set intervals e.g. every 60 minutes 
7) Statistics tell you how many files have been analysed / copied 
8) Statistics tell you if any errors have occurred 
9) A logfile informs you of any problems that have occurred 
10) System tray support. Clone is hidden and doesn't clutter your task bar or desktop 
11) Can be set to automatically start when windows is started 
12) Keep copies of old versions of files which you can go back to later if required 
13) Software developers can keep old version of files for backup and configuration management purposes 
14) Easy to use interface 
15) Help file included</Char_Desc_2000>
</English>
</Program_Descriptions>
<Web_Info>
<Application_URLs>
        <Application_Info_URL>http://newtonsoftware.co.uk/clone</Application_Info_URL>
        <Application_Order_URL>http://newtonsoftware.co.uk/clone/purchase.html</Application_Order_URL>
        <Application_Screenshot_URL>http://newtonsoftware.co.uk/clone/stats.gif</Application_Screenshot_URL>
        <Application_Icon_URL>http://newtonsoftware.co.uk/clone/icon.gif</Application_Icon_URL>
        <Application_XML_File_URL>http://newtonsoftware.co.uk/clone/clone.xml</Application_XML_File_URL>
    </Application_URLs>
<Download_URLs>
        <Primary_Download_URL>http://newtonsoftware.co.uk/clone/cloneInstall.exe</Primary_Download_URL>
        <Secondary_Download_URL />
        <Additional_Download_URL_1 />
        <Additional_Download_URL_2 />
    </Download_URLs>
</Web_Info>
<Permissions>
        <Distribution_Permissions>Clone may be distributed by any 3rd party as long as the installation file remains the same as :-
http://newtonsoftware.co.uk/clone/cloneInstall.exe</Distribution_Permissions>
        <EULA>Copyright and Legal ObligationsCopyright and Legal Obligations 
End User Licence Agreement (EULA) for Clone
SOFTWARE PRODUCT LICENSE
Clone is protected by copyright laws and international copyright treaties, as 
well as other intellectual property laws and treaties. Clone is licensed, not 
sold.
1. GRANT OF LICENSE.
This EULA grants you the following rights with respect to Clone:
Tim Newton grants you an individual, personal, nonexclusive license to make and 
use copies of Clone for the sole purpose of using it. You may install copies of 
Clone on a maximum of 2 computers provided that you are the only 
individual using Clone. If you are an entity, Tim Newton grants you the right to 
designate one individual within your organization to have the right to use Clone 
in the manner provided above.
2. DESCRIPTION OF OTHER RIGHTS AND LIMITATIONS.
- Limitations on Reverse Engineering, Decompilation, and Disassembly.
You may not reverse engineer, decompile, or disassemble the object code portions 
of Clone, except and only to the extent that such activity is expressly 
permitted by applicable law notwithstanding this limitation.
- Software Transfer.
You may permanently transfer all of your rights (not a part of them) under this 
EULA, provided the recipient agrees to the terms of this EULA.
- Termination. Without prejudice to any other rights, Tim Newton may terminate 
this EULA if you fail to comply with the terms and conditions of this EULA. In 
such event, you must destroy all copies of Clone and all of its component parts.
3. COPYRIGHT.
All title and copyrights in and to Clone (including but not limited to any 
images, photographs, animations, video, audio, music, and text incorporated into 
Clone), and any copies of Clone are owned by Tim Newton. Clone is protected by 
copyright laws and international treaty provisions. Therefore, you must treat 
Clone like any other copyrighted material.
LIMITED WARRANTY
NO WARRANTIES.
Tim Newton expressly disclaims any warranty for Clone. Clone and any related 
documentation is provided &quot;as is&quot; without warranty of any kind, either express 
or implied, including, without limitation, the implied warranties or 
merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or noninfringement. The 
entire risk arising out of use or performance of Clone remains with you.
NO LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES.
In no event shall Tim Newton be liable for any damages whatsoever (including, 
without limitation, damages for loss of business profits, business interruption, 
loss of business information, or any other pecuniary loss) arising out of the 
use of or inability to use this product, even if Tim Newton has been advised of 
the possibility of such damages.</EULA>
</Permissions>
<Simtel>
    <Simtel_Agent />
    <Simtel_FORM>Y</Simtel_FORM>
    <Simtel_DOS_Category>Select - MS-DOS Platform (blank)</Simtel_DOS_Category>
    <Simtel_Platform>win95 - Win95/Win98/WinME</Simtel_Platform>
    <Simtel_Category>Utilities/Drivers/Systems Files - diskback Disk / Drive Backup Utilities</Simtel_Category>
    <SIMTEL_FORM_VER>1.6 11/26/2002</SIMTEL_FORM_VER>
</Simtel>
</XML_DIZ_INFO>
